Are they going to the carnival?
Come on, let's follow them.
Jin Ho, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Do you think
I didn't notice you?
Do you want me to kill you
both here?
Why are you following me?
You left this at the eatery
earlier.
That's my girlfriend's.
Don't follow me!
She's really going to take us
to Golda's.
They might be staying there
overnight.
I'll stay here, and you guys
go home.
How can I sleep?
Jin Ho hasn't come home yet.
Why are you so concerned
about Jin Ho?
You should only be worrying
about me.
Wow, clingy?
Fine, you can say I'm clingy!
Well, what can I do? I love you!
You love me? What's that?
You're my best friend, right?
That's why I love you.
Andrew,
my friend replied about the
plate number you're checking.
Who is this registered to?
Vicente Alcala's.
He's the biggest supplier of
ammunition in the Philippines.
That's the M14 and AK-47.
That's for a special client.
This is where you're hiding,
Golda.
Wow, you're really doing
a good job.
That's a big deal for us.
Be careful.
This is a big syndicate.
And with Joey, you take care
of her first.
She hid with another syndicate.
She used her brains.
What's the plan?
We'll wait for her to come out,
then we'll intercept her?
If we just wait for her,
there's no guarantee
when we'll find her.
But we're still pursuing her,
right?
We can't give up,
especially now.
We know where she's hiding.
Well, it looks like we have
no other choice
but to enter Godfather's villa.
It's dangerous.
For sure,
his place is surrounded
by his private army.
We don't have any other choice.
We have to be creative
to get access.
Yeah, but how?
The question is how!
Are you mad at me?
No!
Really?
Okay, Becky, okay.
Thank you.
I'll come up with a proposal,
and I'll e-mail it to you, okay?
Okay, thank you, thank you.
Ma'am, it looks like
we have good news.
Very good news, Clarissa.
Not just for me but for
the people we're helping.
Because I'm trying to look
for a sponsor
to support our monthly feeding
program
and a friend of mine is trying
to connect me
with someone who just might
say yes.
I'll just fix the proposal,
okay?
Ma'am...
Can I talk to you?
This is just about your offer
to me before...
about my husband's case.
Of course. What about it?
I really want to ask
for your husband's help.
Yes, the offer still stands,
so let's do it.
Let's sit down later and talk
about your husband's case.
So I can tell my husband too.
Is that okay?
Yes, thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
The gate is too high.
There's no way from here.
But there's a tree
on the other side.
That's the perfect vantage
point.
But the problem...
Hey.
Stupid.
You stupid.
What?
You're mad.
I know, you're mad.
I knew it. So tell me why.
We can't pull this mission off
if you're acting like this!
I mean, you might as well
go home
and just let me handle it
myself, okay?
Smile, smile.
Hi. Sorry, I don't have anyone
to ask.
I've been going around
for a while now.
Do you know the house
of Vicente Alcala?
Sorry? Vicent...
Why, Miss? Why?
Do you need anything
from our boss?
You work wit him?
Well, it's a good thing.
The events team sent me.
I'm the one who's going
to do the ocular
for his house for his party.
Party...
Yes.
Are you serious?
Did the event organizer
give you this?
Yes.
You know, it's limited.
But you know,
we wouldn't have had that
if Jin Ho had made a mistake.
Right, Jin Ho?
Good thing I had a plan.
This could be our way in,
actually.
What's important is that
we get the guest list,
then we can put our names on it.
Us?
Joey, you're not included,
it's just the three of us.
Why?
Why are you telling me
what to do?
Joey, it's dangerous,
and there's always a problem.
Remember what happened to Golda?
What happened when you
showed up?
It got foiled, remember?
It's not good when there's
a girl around.
And one more thing,
you might get emotional.
Wait a minute?
What's your real issue with me?
Is it because I failed,
or because I'm emotional,
or because I'm a girl?
What? Which one?
Wait, where's that coming from?
I didn't say anything like that.
Can you stop being so sensitive?
You just said it!
And please, I'm not the only one
who's sensitive!
You're the one who is careless
with what you're saying!
You're the one
who's insensitive!
Well, okay, if you don't want me
to come, then don't!
I'll do my own thing.
I'll go alone.
Great!
Why?
Is there something wrong
with what I said?
There's nothing wrong there,
right?
I have no idea.
Joey, have some rice.
Eat first.
Oh, no need, Peter.
Let me do it.
I can handle it,
and just because I'm a girl,
it doesn't mean I'm just
all emotions, right?
What's with this chicken?
I just want to eat,
but I'm just too sensitive.
It's so tough...
Tough...
Tough.
You want water, Joey? Here.
Thank you, Jin Ho.
You're so sweet.
You really care about
my feelings.
Thank you.
Be careful, Joey,
because you don't know...
There are people who feel
like superheroes.
Wrong!
Super wrong!
Do you know those mushrooms?
The ones that appear,
appear, appear
even though you don't need them.
Are you talking about me?
Why? Of course not.
Why would I talk about you?
Then why do you say it
in English,
so I can understand, right?
What do you think?
Are you guys fighting?
-No!
Don't shoult.
There's someone sensitive here.
Be sensitive.
You might hurt someone.
It's up to you.
That's right, you should analyze
the situation
before you say anything.
It's more important to analyze
your egos.
So...
so, I have issues with my ego?
Why? Were you hit?
The chicken is so tough.
Hi, Hon!
The kids?
They've eaten.
They're in the playroom
with Nanny.
Hon...
when's your Hong Kong
conference?
This week. I'll be back
by Wednesday.
Oh, so...
So, five days.
I was just thinking,
if you could help me
with something, Hon?
Well, it's about one
of my employees.
Because her husband is in jail,
and they need assistance.
What kind of assistance?
Well, I was thinking if
you could have someone,
look into his case.
You know, check if
he's eligible for bail
or if there's anything
that can be done.
What's the case?
Murder.
His name is Miguel Delgado.
Former Major Miguel Delgado.
He used to be a police officer,
Hon.
I'll try to see what I can do.
Okay, thank you.
Yo, yo, yo little brother.
What?
Are you not drinking?
No, maybe you shouldn't,
cause you're still a baby.
You know, you need to be
protected by...
Superheroes!
Wow!
Superhero.
Okay, come here.
We haven't started,
and you're drunk.
It's bitter.
You're still a baby.
Delicious.
I'll give you one more shot.
You can do that.
- Andrew! Join us!
- Yes?
Yes! Come on.
Maybe you'll even be Superman
if you drink this.
Fun!
No, thank you. Pass, pass.
I'm going to bed.
- Hey...
- KJ.
Yes, that's right.
Alcohol is dangerous for robots
because they'll become rusty.
They'll lose their feelings
even more.
Game?
What's this?
Soju.
Give me that.
- Why?
- Are you drinking?
You react too much?
Why? What do you think?
I can't drink because
I'm a girl, right?
You're a baby.
- What? Come on! Shot!
- Shot?
- Shot!
Wait, wait. Just take it slow.
Shot!
Bitter...
- It's bitter!
- Look at this.
She works for the Boss's wife.
For how long?
Yvette said it's been a month.
Isn't it dangerous, Boss?
Maybe she'll find out something
about the organization.
What, should I work on it?
No.
We have the upper hand.
As long as she doesn't know,
we can use her against her
husband.
That's right.
He'll suffer even more while
we're playing with his family.
Exactly!
And that's how we burn him
slowly.
No. I will show you
the real one.
- Go, go, go!
- All right!
Go, Jin Ho.
That's how...
Fix it!
Joey! Joey! Come on, come on.
- Go, Joey!
- How? How?
Wait.
Yeah?
You touched my heart.
I'm so touched.
I want to cry.
Okay, let's go. Next!
Next! Who's next?
- Game, truth or dare?
- It's you!
You.
Truth or dare.
Truth.
- Okay, wait, wait.
- Truth.
I have a question.
What's your ideal man?
It's good if there is one.
I like someone kind, loving,
gentle, and sweet.
That's it.
Well, that's all me! That's me.
- Really?
- Yes!
- Crazy!
- How did it become you?
I just don't like someone
arrogant, bossy,
the one who thinks he's always
right,
the one who's so insensitive.
That's it...
someone with a heart of stone.
Yuck! It turns me off.
You know, it's good, Jin Ho,
you're not like that.
Me?
Yeah.
I'm not like that.
Are you saying I'm your ideal
man?
I don't know. Maybe.
I'll just go to the CR.
I'll just go to the CRIS.
I'm just going to pee.
The CR is over here.
He'll use the CRIS in the tree.
Vincent Alcala?
Yes.
Be careful.
This is a big syndicate.
And with Joey,
we know she's impulsive.
She won't easily give up.
You take care of her first.
Andrew, this guy won't respect
you.
Guys, Trigger is here!
Let's continue our party-party!
Yes, it's a party-party
for real!
Trigger!
Ramon Orbos, the cop they say
I killed, do you know him?
Buddy,
can I ask you a favor?
Can you set me up with him?
Do you think he'll give you
time?
Just because you're a cop
out there
doesn't mean you're important
here.
I'm drinking.
Isn't it obvious?
Can you just get out of my face?
Leave me alone. Go away.
You know what?
I really don't understand
why you're mad at me.
- What did I do?
- That's the thing.
You're not doing anything!
But Joey likes everything
you do.
What's that?
Joey?
- Is it...
- Yes, it's about her!
Everything about her!
Because I like her, okay?
But I'm unlucky, she likes you.
What's funny?
- What's funny?
- Okay, listen.
- Listen!
Joey's pretty, yeah?
She's sweet and...
But you don't have
to worry about me.
To be honest, I'm not the one
you should be jealous of.
You like her. I knew it.
That's why.
Last.
Wait, are you still drinking?
Hey, that's enough.
Joey, that's enough,
you're drunk.
Why?
You're drunk, aren't you?
I said that's enough.
You're drunk.
You're really hard-headed.
Here you go again.
Why?
Because...
Because I'm a girl?
That's what you're going to say.
Look, you're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
You know, I didn't say anything
because you're a girl.
What? Because I'm a kid?
Like that?
I'm not belittling you, okay?
So stop that.
You're drunk. Go to sleep.
What do I have to do to make you
stop treating me like a child?
Tell me!
Go to sleep.
I said tell me!
I talked to Trigger.
He agreed to what you wanted.
What do you need from Trigger?
Are you going to ask for help?
You're really fooling me,
aren't you?
Didn't we already talk
about this, Joey?
You're not coming.
What?
Do you have a problem with me
being a woman again, right?
I can fight too.
I'm a black belter.
Remember, your enemies
are gun smugglers.
Good job!
Maybe you've forgotten,
my father is a police officer.
There's a party going on
at the Godfather's.
It looks like the transaction
will happen there.
Then, we need to get in.
An invitation has arrived
from one of our target sponsors.
We cannot miss this opportunity,
right?
The theme is The Great Gatsby.
I don't have anything to wear.
We didn't prepare.
Costume? Wait.